caretoclick.com 2013-05-11

# Care To Click

### Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

**Last modified: June 27, 2012**

Below you will find the privacy policy for CaretoClick.com, Care2Click.com and certain other applications, software or functionality through which you have accessed this Privacy Policy (collectively, “CaretoClick”).  Please note that, in this privacy policy, Care to Click, LLC may be referred to as “we,” “us,” or “our.”

We have created this privacy policy to disclose our most current policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of information collected from you, and answer your questions regarding our privacy practices.

**_Information We Collect_**

_We May Receive and Collect Your Personally Identifiable Information_.  Personally identifiable information generally includes information that could be used to determine your identity, such as your name, address, phone number, e-mail address, and birth date.  The term “personally identifiable information” does not include anonymous information such as IP address information.  You can access and use portions of CaretoClick without providing any personally identifiable information.  However, you may choose to provide us with personally identifiable information within certain features of CaretoClick, such as within our “contact us” form.  If you are located outside of the United States, any information you provide to us will be transferred to the United States. The following are some examples of how we may receive and collect your personally identifiable information:

·         We may collect personally identifiable information from you if you choose to register for a CaretoClick account.  You will need to register with us and set up an account in order to use all of the features of CaretoClick.  You will need to share certain information with us, such as your name and email address, as well as create a user name and password, to set up an account, and we will collect this information that you provide. 

·         We may collect personally identifiable information from you if you choose to fill out any forms (including but not limited to forms related to the “Get Free Stuff” links), profiles, or surveys on CaretoClick.

·         We may collect personally identifiable information from you if you choose to sign up for our email newsletter(s).

·         If you send us correspondence, such as emails or letters, we may choose to collect information about you within such correspondence.

·         We may receive your personally identifiable information from one of our business partners or other third-party sources.

_We May Receive and Collect_ _Non-Personally Identifiable Information_ :  We may collect non-personally identifiable information about you through a variety of technical methods, including the following: 

·         **Collection of IP Address.**   When you visit CaretoClick, we may collect your IP address.  We may use IP addresses to collect information such as the frequency with which individuals visit various parts of CaretoClick. 

·         **Collection via Social Media.** We may collect information that you authorize us to access or that is publicly available through social media platforms such as Facebook and Twitter.

·         **Collection with Cookies.**   "Cookies" are pieces of information that a Web site sends to your computer while you are viewing a Web site. We may set and access cookies on your computer to track and store preferential information about you.  Please note that most Internet browsers will allow you to stop cookies from being stored on your computer and to delete cookies stored on your computer.

·         **Collection with Web beacons.   **“Web beacons” are electronic images, tags or scripts that allow a Web site to access cookies and help track general usage patterns of visitors to a Web site.  Web beacons can recognize certain types of information, such as cookies, time and date of a page view, and a description of the page where the Web beacon is placed. 

_The_ _information collected through these technical methods standing alone, cannot be used to determine your identity_.  Such information may, however, be combined in a way that makes it become personally identifiable information.  If this happens, we will treat the combined information as personally identifiable information.

_Collection of Information from Minors_

CaretoClick is intended to be accessed and used only by adults and is not directed to children under the age of 18. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information by anyone under the age of 18 and you should not provide us with any information regarding any individual under the age of 18. 

_How We Use Personally Identifiable Information_

We use your personally identifiable information in the following ways:

·         to fulfill your requests for certain products, services or information;

·         to contact you and deliver information to you such as administrative notices, offerings, and other communications relevant to your use of CaretoClick;

·         to analyze site usage, conduct market research, improve marketing and promotional efforts, and improve and customize our content, layout, products and services;

·         to provide customer support and troubleshoot and resolve problems and disputes;

·         to try to detect and protect against error, fraud or other criminal activity, to enforce our Terms of Use available at the URL www.caretoclick.com/terms (the “Terms of Use”), for other internal purposes, and as otherwise described to you at the time of collection;

·         for direct marketing purposes;

·         for online behavioral advertising;

·         for any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information; and

·         as otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy.

_How We Disclose or Share Your Personally Identifiable Information_

There are various circumstances in which we may disclose or share your personally identifiable information with third parties. 

_Disclosure in the Normal Scope of Business_ : The following describes some of the ways that your personally identifiable information may be disclosed in the normal scope of business:

·         If you register with us, we may place your user name on the Site.  You should not provide a user name that you do not want to be visible and accessible by others.

·         If you permit us to access information you post on social media platforms, we may include your image(s) (“Your Images”) on our Site (such as on our “Champion’s Wall”) or other social media content.  Your Images may be visible and accessible to us and others, including search engines. 

·         We may aggregate personally identifiable information and disclose such information in a non-personally identifiable manner to advertisers and other third parties for their marketing and promotional purposes.

·         We may disclose your personally identifiable information to third parties to market their products or services to you and for other purposes.  You understand that we may sell, rent, share, and disclose any information you provide to us or through CaretoClick.  In certain cases, we may allow you to opt out of such sale and disclosure of your personally identifiable information.  If you opt out, the Referral Fees (defined in the Terms of Use) that we would otherwise receive may be reduced and therefore, the corresponding Donation (defined in the Terms of Use) will also be reduced.

·         We may use third parties that we refer to as internal service providers to facilitate or outsource one or more aspects of our business, product and service operations and therefore we may provide some of your personal information directly to these internal service providers.

Please note that if you provide information to a third-party service provider directly, then the service provider’s use of your personally identifiable information is governed by the service provider’s privacy policy. You should evaluate the practices of service providers before deciding to provide information directly to a service provider.

_Disclosure in the Event of a Transfer_ :  Personally identifiable information and other personal information collected from or about you may also be transferred to a third party as a result of a sale, acquisition, merger, reorganization, other transfer or bankruptcy (a “Transfer”) involving us.  We specifically reserve the right, at any time, to transfer personally identifiable information collected from or residing within CaretoClick, and any of its databases, as well as any part or all of our business and/or assets, to affiliates or third parties in connection with a Transfer. 

_Disclosure in Extenuating Circumstances_ :  We may also share or disclose your personally identifiable information and other personal information collected from or about you if we determine that the disclosure of your personally identifiable information is necessary in the following circumstances: (1) you are or may be violating this Privacy Policy or our Terms of Use;  (2) you are interfering with another's rights or property, including our rights or property; (3) you are violating any applicable law, rule or regulation; (4) where applicable law, rule or regulation requires it; and/or (5) if requested by authorities in the event of any act such as terrorism or an instance of local, regional or national emergency. 

_Cancellation of Your Account_

You may cancel your CaretoClick account at any time.  If you cancel your CaretoClick account, we may, in our sole discretion, choose to continue to make any information or content provided to us (including, without limitation, your user name and Your Images) available to others, including search engines.  For example, through your CaretoClick account, you may post or provide information to us and share it or other content with others.  When you cancel your account, we may determine, in our sole discretion, to keep such content visible within CaretoClick on our Site, such as information and content that may be displayed on our “Champion’s Wall.”  We may also determine, in our sole discretion, to not continue to make such content available to others. 

_How You Can Opt-Out of Receiving Email from Us_

You may opt out of receiving communications via email from us by following the unsubscribe instructions that accompany such communications. 

_Security Measures We Have in Place to Protect Your Information_

We are committed to protecting the security of your personal information from unauthorized disclosure. Please note, however, that no security measures are impenetrable and it is possible that your information may be unlawfully intercepted, accessed or “hacked,” despite our reasonable efforts to prevent it.

_Privacy Policy of Third Party Web Sites_

CaretoClick may include links to other third party Web sites. Such links are not an endorsement or recommendation by us of those Web sites and/or the products or services offered there. Third party Web sites may have different privacy policies and we are not responsible for the privacy practices of those third party Web sites. If you click on a link to a third party Web site, we encourage you to check the privacy policy of that Web site, as it may differ substantially from that of this Privacy Policy.

_Changes to this Privacy Policy_

We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time.  Amendments will take effect immediately upon us posting the updated Privacy Policy on CaretoClick.  You are encouraged to revisit this Privacy Policy from time to time in order to review any changes that have been made. The date on which this Privacy Policy was last updated will be noted immediately above this Privacy Policy. 

**_How to Contact Us Regarding this Privacy Policy_**

You can direct any questions concerning this Privacy Policy to us here

**_Special Notification for California Residents – Your California Privacy Rights_**

Individuals who are residents of California and have provided their personally identifiable information to us may request information regarding our disclosures, if any, of their personally identifiable information to third parties for direct marketing purposes.  Such requests must be submitted to us here or at:

Care to Click, LLC

PO Box 1150

Boynton Beach, FL 33425

California privacy rights requests must include the reference “Request for California Privacy Information” on the subject line and in the body of the message and must include the e-mail address or mailing address, as applicable, for us to send our response. This request may be made no more than once per calendar year. We reserve the right not to respond to requests submitted other than to the address specified in this paragraph. 

You may opt out of us disclosing your personally identifiable information to third parties for direct marketing purposes, at no cost to you, by sending a written request to:

Care to Click, LLC

PO Box 1150

Boynton Beach, FL 33425

### Start here, to track your favourite causes.
